Ready or not,
here I come.
[SUMBAKKOKJIL]
Anyone who wants to play hide-and-seek, gather around here.
[In the middle of the night at a waterpark, where there is only quiet darkness,]
[a strange game begins]
Hello?!
Anyone there?
Is there anyone next to me?
What is this?
Oh, no!
Has it been released? The seeker?
[When you hear the footsteps, it's already too late]
It’s coming.
It’s coming. x2
Help me!
Hey, hurry up and hide.
[The seeker is only coming closer]
Why are you guys all coming here?
This does not look good.
What if we get all caught?
Hey, GYU VIN!
Oh!
[SUMBAKKOKJIL]
Woah.
What is this?
Huh?
Ah, is this a gym?
[In the midst of a gloomy atmosphere]
A corpse...!
I think there’s a corpse.
What!
Woah, I got goosebumps.
It genuinely feels like Gonjiam.
Ah, out of all places why here…?
Why did they leave us here?
Eh?!
It looks super scary!
Wow...
What are we supposed to do?
What the?
Ha...
[Each ZEROBASEONE member wakes up in different locations]
What the...
[Member’s current location]
[Locker Room A - HAN YU JIN, RICKY]
[Sauna - PARK GUN WOOK, Sports Center- SEOK MATTHEW]
[Water park - ZHANG HAO, Swimming pool- SUNG HAN BIN,
Locker Room B - KIM GYU VIN, Prison- KIM TAE RAE
[2nd floor Karaoke room - KIM JI WOONG]
Has it started?
[Phone alarm]
Didn't a message come?
From now on, find the key that is inside the ( ).
If caught by the seeker, use the key to be released or
to save other members.
(One key allows for one escape)
If you get caught by the seeker, use the key to escape...
Can I leave?
[2nd floor Karaoke room - KIM JI WOONG]
Okay, okay.
[Sound of special effects activating]
Ha.. this is really...
Woah!
It’s just a sofa!
[Sound of special effects activating]
Ah, what is this?!
[JI WOONG,disoriented amidst
the chaotic situation]
Ah... this is really crazy.
The key...
I think there might be one here.
[Gym Entrance]
[Trap]
[Another disoriented person]
[Sports Center → Lobby - SEOK MATTHEW]
[There’s nothing but pitch-black darkness ahead of him]
Where am I supposed to go?
[Sound of the automatic door opening]
[SEOK MATTHEW]
[Heads to Locker Room A]
[Locker Room  A - HAN YU JIN]
From now on, please look for the keys.
Where are the keys?
Inside? Inside where?
[Sound of special effects activating]
What is that!
Has it been released?
The seeker?
Please.
Please...
I beg you...
[← Lights visible from afar]
Who is that!
It’s me, MATTHEW!
[MATTHEW and YU JIN meets at Locker Room A]
MATTHEW, MATTHEW!
You scared me.
Hey, this is super scary.
Hey, just hide here first!
What are we going to do!
This(= the light) is super bright...
I know, right?
It’s so dark, I can’t see.
That’s true.
There was something on the floor.
I stepped on it and
it made a weird sound ...
There’s also a trap!
There’s a trap?
Oh, where I was, there was a gym.
Then, did you make it all the way here from there?
You have to go like this.
I came from there!
How are we supposed to get out?
How?
Aren’t we supposed to get out?
Are you going to leave?
(The keys) We have to find them!
Find what?
You didn’t see the message?
Did you say a knife?
The message!
Ah, there was a message?
Yes, there was a message. It came just now.
(The message) What does it mean?
What does it mean?
Find the key that is hidden inside somewhere.
Inside where?
Inside...?
(First) Let’s get out.
Hey!
You go first!
Go first!
Let’s go!
[Locker Room A → Snack bar- SEOK MATTHEW, HAN YU JIN]
[Swimming pool - SUNG HAN BIN]
Where is the exit?
Where is it?
Here...
[HAN BIN exits the small pool]
[Outside, a vast Water park]
Because it’s a Water park,
Oh!
That scared me!
wouldn’t it be inside the rides?
What is that…?
I don’t like scary places.
What the... this is scary...
Let’s go.
[Water park - ZHANG HAO]
[ZHANG HAO, SUNG HAN BIN]
Ah, you scared me.
[HAN BIN discovers HAO who is surprised]
Did you find something?
There’s someone here!
Ah, it’s just the producer.
There’s nothing there, right?
Yup.
But because it’s a Water park,
- wouldn’t it be inside the rides?
- Oh.
Then, let’s look there.
But it says it’s inside somewhere.
Inside.
[A funny feeling of someone watching them]
Isn’t in the water, maybe?
Inside the water?
Oh! You may be right.
Hold on.
How are we supposed to find it in the water?
I don’t think we can go in.
If we can, then I’m willing to go in.
Maybe somewhere here?
I’m scared.
I think I might curse.
Oh?!
Who are you?
[Human shaped tube ↓]
A corpse.
Someone is tied up.
What if...
that happens to us?
No way it can be inside that human figure?
[HAN BIN shakes the tube]
What are you doing? LOL
What are you doing?
Hey, let’s not be ...
exposing ourselves in this big area.
There’s nowhere to hide.
Then let’s find somewhere to hide.
Ah, great idea.
[Sauna - PARK GUN WOOK]
The key.
[Sound of door opening]
[GUN WOOK heads outside]
[Cafeteria - PARK GUN WOOK]
I really want to find the members.
[Immediately GUN WOOK finds someone]
[It was GYU VIN]
It’s a Water park.
[← PARK GUN WOOK]
[GYU VIN, only focused on finding the keys]
[Finally sees GUN WOOK]
Hey, there’s a balloon floating over there.
Aren’t we supposed to pop that?
But it said to find it inside of something.
I know, I’m positive it’s that balloon over there.
Let’s go over there and shake it.
Ah, okay!
There is something inside here!
GUN WOOK, there is something in here!
[The yellow balloon that caught GUN WOOK’s eyes]
I think there’s nothing in here.
There’s nothing?
I think they just left it here.
It’s just nothing.
Hey, GUN WOOK
shouldn’t we go find YU JIN?
He might’ve fainted by now.
[YU JIN with MATTHEW]
[Snack bar - SEOK MATTHEW, HAN YU JIN]
Hey, there’s ice cream.
YU JIN!
Yes?
Did you find something?
Have some ice cream.
Wow! Ice cream!
I want this one.
But, are we allowed to eat this?
I think it’s fine.
[※ Filmed with prior permission]
Now what?
I don’t know.
I don’t think it’s over here...
Ah, that scared me!
[JI WOONG getting startled multiple times right from the start]
[Even though he’s scared, he still doesn’t give up]
[2nd floor Cave Room - KIM JI WOONG]
Oh!
OMG! OMG! I found it!
[KIM JI WOONG finds the key inside the Cave Room]
This is insane. Hold on.
[Moves to a different location]
Hey!
What are you doing?
[Approaching JI WOONG, who only looks straight ahead]
[TAE RAE]
Hey! What was that for!
[Both of them giggling]
Hey, TAE RAE!
Did you find the key?
Did you?
Where did you find it?
Inside that Cave Room.
One? Only one?
Only one!
Now, we need to find somewhere to hide.
Somewhere to hide?
I think we should head downstairs.
Hold on!
There’s not enough places to hide here.
We have to head downstairs.
[JI WOONG heads down
from the 2nd floor Sauna]
[1st floor - KIM JI WOONG]
Hey, what is that?!
[← HAN YU JIN]
Did you see this?
Why?
Open it.
Why! Why?
I think...
there’s something inside here.
I think the key is inside here.
[The ‘thing’ that looks extremely suspicious ↓]
There’s something inside there. X2
[A loud noise from afar]
My ice cream!
You stepped on it.
[Leaving the ice cream behind]
Be careful.
[The three people approaches the weird “thing”]
Isn’t it a real human being?
Ah! Hey.
Who started from here?
[← PARK GUN WOOK’s blindfold]
There’s a blindfold. It’s starting. It’s starting.
[Leaving without any gains]
[← KIM TAE RAE]
[KIM TAE RAE giggling]
[After accomplishing his mission, he starts to find somewhere to hide]
[↑ Where the members are gathered]
Huh?
What is this?
Everyone is just goofing off?
What are they doing over there?
How do we go there?
[Meanwhile at the Water park]
Uh, it’s shining?!
Oh?!
Is it there?
What is that?
Wow, I found a key!
What should we do! What should we do!
I’ll hold this for you!
I’ll go get it.
You can do it. You can do it!
Oh! This... x2
Should I hold this for you?
Yes, please.
Can you see it?
[The key tied to the balloon string →]
Uh? Hold on.
Ah, that scared me.
[← PARK GUN WOOK suddenly appears]
The key isn’t there!
[GUN WOOK, who earlier checked the balloons with GYU VIN]
I’ve checked already.
There’s nothing.x3
No, there’s something.
The key? Oh, you’re right.
[SUNG HAN BIN finds the key inside the water]
[Phone alarm]
I guess there’s only one.
A message came for the key hint.
[Hint for the key]
- Hint for the key? Where?
- Here.x3
Do you know where this is?
No.
Where is that?
[The three are deciding the next destination]
Should we just go first?
There’s nothing here, right?
- There’s nothing...
- Yes.
[Sound of special effects activating]
Ahh!
[Decides to move somewhere else]
That really scared me...
[1st floor Cafeteria → 2nd floor Cafeteria - KIM GYU VIN]
The members that I haven’t seen yet are
RICKY
[GYU VIN heads to the storage room that’s located in the corner of the cafeteria]
Hehehehe
Hey, what are you doing? Come out!
What are you doing? Just come out!
[Finds RICKY who has been hiding]
I was actually talking about you.
What were you talking about?
What were you doing?
Were you sitting there this whole time to scare me?
No, I was just hiding this whole time.
I thought… someone was outside.
So, I just hid myself.
[Takes off his blindfold]
[RICKY heard the sound of special effects activating]
There’s constant noise nearby...
[Enters a storage room nearby]
[Hides himself in the hiding spot]
Who is that?
Why do they keep on making loud noises?
Who do we have to hide from?
I don’t know either.
[Sound of special effects activating]
This sound is really worth being scared of.
I was hiding this whole time because of that sound.
[The timer has not started yet]
[Only 2 keys have been found so far]
Why can’t we find the keys?
What is that sound?
What was that?
Please save me.
[While everyone is struggling]
Huh?
What?
It’s over there.
- Underneath the tube...
- Oh?!
Am I wrong?
No, you’re right!
[The two finds the tube in the hint]
- Here?
- Oh?!
[ZHANG HAO finds the key inside the tube]
[Phone alarm]
[Hint for the key]
It’s in the vending machine!
[The next hint arrives just in time]
Where is the vending machine?
It was over there.
Up there! Where the swimming pool was.
[YU JIN leads the way up to the swimming pool]
Hey, hey, now there’s a ton of dry ice spread out here.
You’re right.
It’s gotten worse. I hope it’s not time for...
No way...
Right now?
[ZEROBASEONE are gathered in the Water park]
Did you find the key?
I couldn’t find it.
I did find one.
I think
there is no one (the seeker) here right now, right?
Yeah, I think so too.
Don’t you think they’re going to give us time to find all the keys?
Ah, the vending machine is over there.
Ah~
[Vending machine ↓]
But doesn’t it mean that
the seeker will start looking for us
when we find some of the keys?
That’s right.
[RICKY heads towards the members
at the fork of the road]
[YU JIN heads to the vending machine]
What was that?
[HAN YU JIN: I see]
[HAN YU JIN:  the vending machine]
[Puts his hand inside the vending machine]
You found me.
[HAN YU JIN’s scream]
Now, I’m the seeker.
Ready or not,
here I come.
[Water park - SUNG HAN BIN, SEOK MATTHEW, PARK GUN WOOK,
ZHANG HAO, RICKY, HAN YU JIN]
[The members hid themselves as soon as the seeker woke up]
Huh?!
What is it? x3 Help me!
Hey!
[HAN BIN and HAO hides in the supply rental center]
[Lobby - KIM JI WOONG]
JI WOONG who was at the hotel lobby hides behind the sofa
[TAE RAE who was at the water park heads to the shower room]
Help me.
[Member’s current location]
[Water park - SUNG HAN BIN, SEOK MATTHEW, PARK GUN WOOK,
ZHANG HAO, RICKY, HAN YU JIN]
[Shower room - KIM TAE RAE]
[Lobby - KIM JI WOONG]
[Locker Room B - KIM GYU VIN]
[The hide-and-seek now begins]
[KIM JI WOONG ↓]
[Phone alarm]
The hide-and-seek now begins.
The playtime is 4,444 seconds.
If you get caught by the seeker, you will be instantly taken to prison.
If you get caught by the seeker,
you will be instantly taken to prison.
The survival rate is very important in this game.
If the survival rate is more than 50%,
ZEROSE will be awarded with a big gift.
So, please try your best to stay alive.
Ready or not,
here I come.
I’m scared... x2
Ready or not,
[YU JIN returns to Locker Room A where he first woke up]
here I come.
Please, please.
[Locker Room A - HAN YU JIN]
[The seeker]
[Supply rental center - SUNG HAN BIN, ZHANG HAO,
RICKY, PARK GUN WOOK]
[The seeker heads to the supply rental center
where the four members are hiding]
What is that?
Someone is here.
[PARK GUN WOOK →]
[Supply rental center →]
[The seeker ↓]
[The seeker]
[SUNG HAN BIN, ZHANG HAO, RICKY, PARK GUN WOOK]
[Almost in front of him]
[Supply rental center →]
[Luckily, the seeker changed its direction]
It’s not safe here.
[The seeker enters Locker Room A where YU JIN is hiding]
What was that sound?
(The seeker) It’s here. It’s here.
Ahhh!
Please.
[HAN YU JIN, I found you!]
I’m scared.
I’m sorry.
[Screams heard faintly]
Upstairs...
I think it’s upstairs.
[KIM JI WOONG sneezing]
I think this is much better.
[If you can't escape from prison within 20 minutes,
you won't be able to leave until the game ends.]
One of your members has been captured.
RICKY!
Yes.
Do you have a key?
Nope.
Why are you so confident?
Do you have a key?
- We do
- Yes.
[Locker Room B - KIM GYU VIN]
[In the meantime, GYU VIN hides in Locker Room B]
[Hint for the key]
[Searching for the key within the hint]
[KIM GYU VIN finds the key inside the locker]
[Locker Alarm]
I took out the key.
[GYU VIN runs into MATTHEW and GUN WOOK]
You scared me.
I found a key.
Already?
What are we going to do?
How are we supposed to find all the keys
in this huge place?
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps]
[The three decides to disperse]
[2nd floor Sauna KIM GYU VIN →]
[1st floor Sauna SEOK MATTHEW →]
[2nd floor KIM GYU VIN]
I’m doomed now that we are all scattered.
Oh,no. I’m scared
[KIM TAE RAE →]
[The seeker’s scream]
[The seeker passes by TAE RAE without noticing him]
[The seeker and KIM GYU VIN on the 2nd floor]
[GYU VIN checks to see the seeker’s location]
[Slowly moves to another location]
[KIM GYU VIN ↑]
Wow…I’m scared.
How to escape from prison?
'Please request rescue via message to the members'
So, there is a way to escape.
[HAN YU JIN: I’m in prison and]
[HAN YU JIN: I only have 3,500 seconds left.]
[HAN YU JIN: Please come rescue me.]
[KIM TAE RAE: I don’t have a key.]
[KIM TAE RAE: Someone who has a key needs to go.]
[KIM JI WOONG ↓]
[The only person who has a key]
The key that’s inside the...
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps]
[KIM JI WOONG ↓]
[The seeker, KIM JI WOONG]
[Sound of the automatic door opening]
[KIM JI WOONG, I found you!]
I found you!
Ah...
I’m slightly annoyed...
YU JIN
You’re captured?
Yes.
JI WOONG has been captured.
[HAN YU JIN: JI WOONG has been captured.]
[HAN YU JIN: Two people are now captured.]
[KIM TAE RAE: Hahahahahaha]
[KIM JI WOONG: We’re clearly going to fail.]
[KIM TAE RAE: I’m still at the Water park.]
[KIM TAE RAE: I can’t go.]
[PARK GUN WOOK: Yes, you can.]
I don’t think the seeker is here.
[ZHANG HAO →]
Hey! Hey! GYU VIN
the seeker isn’t here, right?
It’s not here. It’s not here.
The seeker is a clown.
What is that?
clown.
(Cheek) Here?
Ah, not that...
clown, clown.
You also have a key right?
I do.
I also have a key too.
So, we need to be the ones saving people.
[Meanwhile, TAE RAE checks outside]
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps]
[The seeker carefully checks inside]
[But, just leaves?]
[The sound of the seeker’s footsteps fading away]
[SUMBAKKOKJIL]